bet9ja.com 2019-11-04

# Bet9ja Nigeria Sport Betting,Premier League Odds,Casino,Bet

KC Gaming Networks Limited (“Bet9ja”, “we”, “us” or “our”) will treat the data you provide us with as private and shall only use it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and process your personal information through your use of our website (the “site”) and your online account you open with us (the “Account”), to create your Account profile, to ensure security of the website and to enable you to use the products and the Account (collectively the “Services”). For the purposes of the Services, Bet9ja is the data controller of your Personal Data.

### **I. PERSONAL DATA**

All references to ‘Personal Data’ in this Privacy Policy refer to any personal information about a natural person which enables that individual to be identified directly or indirectly by reference to the data provided.

The Personal Data we receive helps us provide, personalize, and continually improve the Services. We use the information to enable you to use the Services, process payments, communicate with you about your Account activity, products, services and promotional offers, update our records and maintain your Account with us, display content, and recommend our products and services that might be of interest to you. We also use this information to improve our Services, prevent, detect or report fraud or abuses of our Services and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical, or other functions on our behalf.

**Information you give us:**  we collect the following information when you open an Account with us: first name, surname, gender, date of birth, place of birth, postal address, email address, phone number, language, currency, a valid original copy of an official document bearing his names and photographs (passport or ID card). You may give us additional information that qualifies as Personal Data as part of your use of the Account and/or any of the Services.

**Automatic Information:**  We automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies," and other unique identifiers and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser or device accesses our Services. Refer to your Web browser cookies setting options for more information how to manage your cookies settings. Please note that we may not be able to provide you with all the site features and Services functionalities should you block or reject the cookies.

**Information from other sources:**  We may receive information about you from other sources (such as from the payment providers or third party identity verification service provider) and add it to your Account information and only according to this Privacy Policy.

You will also be required to provide login details of your choice, namely a username, password which will be kept by us. We additionally require you to provide us with a payment method and payment details (such as bank transfer, credit card or another acceptable means of payment) in order that you can credit your Account and make the withdrawals.

You can access a broad range of information about your Account and your interactions with us, including your Personal Data. You may access that information about you by logging into your Account. You also have the right to access your personal data at any time in order to make alterations to any personal information that may have changed or become obsolete. Should you believe that any personal information we hold for you is incorrect, please [contact our customer services here.](https://account.bet9ja.com/messaging/ContactUs)

###  **II. USE OF PERSONAL DATA**

We process your Personal Data to operate, provide and improve the Services. These purposes include:

  * **Use of Bet9ja products and your Account:**  We use your Personal Data to process your bets, payments to and from Account and communicate with you about gaming activity, products, services, and promotional offers.
  * **Provide, troubleshoot, and improve the Service:**   We use your Personal Data to provide functionality, analyse performance, fix errors, and improve usability and effectiveness of the Services.
  * **Recommendations:**  We may use your Personal Data to recommend features, products, and services that might be of interest to you and to identify your preferences.
  * **Comply with legal and contractual requirements:**  In certain cases, we are required by law to collect and process your Personal Data.
  * **Communicate with you:** We use your personal information to communicate with you in relation to the Services via different channels (e.g., by phone, email, chat).
  * **Advertising:**  We may use your personal information to display interest-based ads for features, products, and services that might be of interest to you.
  * **Fraud Prevention:**  We process information to prevent or detect fraud and abuse in order to protect the security of our customers, Bet9ja, and others.

**III. WILL BET9JA DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL DATA?**

  * **Making payments:** depending on which payment service you use, you may need to disclose your Personal Data or part of it to your payment provider. Note that the payment provider already has your Personal Data to provide you with the payment services and their use of any Personal Data disclosed by us will be regulated by the payment provider’s privacy policy.
  * **Third-parties service providers** : We engage with the technology providers, financial institutions, other companies, and individuals to perform functions on our behalf and transactions that you request or authorize. Examples include sending e-mail, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payment transactions, verifying identity, fraud screening, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes and must process the personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted by the applicable data protection legislation. Such third party service providers may be based outside of Nigeria in the jurisdictions, including the EEA jurisdictions, that provide adequate levels of protection of personal data.
  * **Advertising and Third-party Analytics providers:** We may display interest-based ads to you when you are using Facebook through advertising tools offered by Facebook. We do not share any of your Personal Data with Facebook as the tools Facebook operates allows us to convert your email address to a unique identifier to match the unique identifiers Facebook generates from the email addresses of its users. We may also use third party analytics providers, including Google, to collect information about the usage of our Services and to enable us to improve how our Services work. Google Analytics and comparable providers use cookies and other similar technologies to collect information about the usage of our Services and to report website trends to us.  
  * **Business Transfers** : As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy other businesses or services. In such transactions, user or other customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. Also, in the unlikely event that Bet9ja or substantially all of its assets are acquired, user information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
  * **Protection of Bet9ja and Others:**  We disclose Account and other Personal Data when we believe disclosure is appropriate or required to comply with the law; enforce or apply our General Terms and Conditions and other agreements we have with you; or protect the rights, property, or safety of our business, our users, or others. This also includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection reduction as well as sharing information with our attorneys, auditors, and other representatives.

Bet9ja shall in no manner whatsoever be held responsible for the manner in which third parties process and/or store the personal data of our customers.

Bet9ja shall only be responsible for its obligations to you in relation to your Personal Data as the data controller under the applicable laws and it does not warrant the standard of the privacy policies of any of the third parties.

Our Services may include third-party advertising and links to other websites and apps.  We do not provide any personally identifiable user information to these advertisers or third-party web sites. If you access a page via a link on our site which takes you to an external website, you take time to read through the privacy policy of the new website which you enter.

**IV. SECURITY**

We design our systems with your security and privacy in mind.

  * We work to protect the security of your information you provide to our web sites by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software to encrypt that information during transmission.
  * We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage, and disclosure of personal customer information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.
  * It is important for you to take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your account and your password. You should keep your password and any security questions confidential. The security of your Account relies on your protection of your password and security questions. DO NOT SHARE YOUR PASSWORD. If you do share your password with a third party for any reason, the third party may have access to your account and your personal information, and you may be responsible for actions taken using your password. If you believe someone else has obtained access to your password, please change it immediately and also contact us right away.

**V. PERSONAL DATA RETENTION**

We keep your Personal Data to enable your continued use of the Service, for as long as it is required in order to fulfil the relevant purposes described in this Privacy Policy, as may be required by law such as for anti-money laundering and counter terrorist financing, tax and accounting purposes, or as otherwise communicated to you. This applies to us retaining your data after you close the Account.

**VI. PROTECTION OF MINORS**

The online betting and gaming services that we offer are strictly prohibited for persons less than 18 years of age or under the age of legal consent for using online betting and gaming services under the laws of the jurisdiction in which the person is located.

Consequently, minors may not register and play on our Site. We collect proof of identification from our customers as part of our age verification process.

Any minor who is found to be gambling on Bet9ja shall have his/her Account immediately blocked. Bet9ja reserves the right to conduct a security review to validate your identity and age. Registration of the Account authorizes us to conduct such security reviews supplied by you against third party databases.

**VII. GENERAL**

Bet9ja shall take no responsibility whatsoever for events beyond its control inclusive of, but not limited to, acts of god or natural disasters and including power cuts and strikes.

Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your Account. It may become necessary, at any time, for us to make modifications to this Privacy Policy and we will publish such modifications on the website. Continued use of the Services will be considered as your acceptance thereof. Such modifications will not impact your Account registration details unless required to the contrary by law.

It is the responsibility of each customer to regularly check the General Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy for updates.

The laws of Nigeria shall govern this Privacy Policy.

**_This Privacy Policy is effective from 22/01/2019_**
